<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JWen&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://dwla.github.io/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on JWen&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://dwla.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Add an Audio to Hugo with MetingJS</title>
      <link>https://dwla.github.io/en/2024/08/add-audio-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dwla.github.io/en/2024/08/add-audio-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents Make code block collapsible in Hugo Add an audio to Hugo with MetingJS Byproducts of web searching This post is a collection of notes made in the past few days, finding the way to add music to Hugo. These notes cover a wide range of topics, listed in the Table of Contents and ordered in an easily-understood manner. Failures (or Mistakes) are also included, because (from Yihui&amp;rsquo;s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Write Hugo Posts with OrgMode and ox-hugo</title>
      <link>https://dwla.github.io/en/2024/07/write-hugo-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dwla.github.io/en/2024/07/write-hugo-blog/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents Why I want to write a blog? OrgMode + ox-hugo Other references unrelated to &amp;ldquo;OrgMode + ox-hugo&amp;rdquo; Why I want to write a blog? Writing a blog is not the thing that most people would do. I have never thought of it, even though I get lots of valuable information from blogs written by other people. Such information cover various aspects, including courage if you encounter career</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a Blog with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://dwla.github.io/en/2024/07/build-hugo-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dwla.github.io/en/2024/07/build-hugo-blog/</guid>
      <description>OS: macOS Ventura 13.2.1 Hugo site directory: ~/Desktop/blog Hugo theme: hugo-ivy Hugo - getting started Install Hugo from Homebrew&#xA;brew install hugo hugo version Create a site skeleton&#xA;cd ~/Desktop hugo new site blog Get a theme met your taste&#xA;cd blog git clone https://github.com/yihui/hugo-ivy themes/hugo-ivy To view the exampleSite (if it exists) of your selected theme&#xA;hugo server --source themes/hugo-ivy/exampleSite --themesDir ../../ View and configure the site&#xA;Copy the configuration file config.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
